{
    "id": "3d9aae6b33e742d383889e20bfd76efe",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Though we are good friends, our views …….. in certain matters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "different",
                "differ",
                "differing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The President gave away the ……… awards at a special function.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gallant",
                "gallantry"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge was not satisfied with the lawyer’s …………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "argue",
                "arguing",
                "argument"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We should be careful to preserve the …………. of the religious places.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sanction",
                "sanctify",
                "sanctity"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The cricket match between India and Pakistan was an …………. one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "excite",
                "excitement",
                "exciting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Most of the road accidents ………….. as a result of careless driving .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occur",
                "occurring",
                "occurrence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She cried …………. for help when she was attacked by robbers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "frantic",
                "frantical",
                "frantically"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Their ………… was proved wrong.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "assume",
                "assumption"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "9 We had a ………… holiday by the sea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "delight",
                "delightful"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not like his ……….. behavior.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "insolence",
                "insolent"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}